You may feel a little prick.
Cult of Chucky is a horror, thriller film directed by Don Mancini.
Confined to an asylum for the criminally insane for the past four years, Nica is
wrongly convinced that she, not Chucky, murdered her entire family...
until a string of grisly deaths occur after her psychiatrist
introduces a new group therapy tool -- a "Good Guy" doll.
Nica Pierce, played by Fiona Dourif.
Chucky (voice), played by Brad Dourif.
Andy Barclay, played by Alex Vincent.
Tiffany Valentine, played by Jennifer Tilly.
Dr. Foley, played by Michael Therriault.
Michael, played by Adam Hurtig.
Cult of Chucky is a 2017 American supernatural slasher
film written and directed by Don Mancini.
The seventh mainline installment of the Child's Play franchise, following the 2013 film Curse of Chucky, it stars Fiona
Dourif, Michael Therriault, Adam Hurtig, Alex Vincent, and Jennifer Tilly with Brad Dourif as the voice of Chucky.
Cult of Chucky began production in Winnipeg, Manitoba, Canada in January 2017 and
premiered at the London FrightFest Film Festival on August 24 the same year.
As with the previous film, it was released direct-to-video by Universal
Pictures Home Entertainment via Blu-ray, DVD and VOD on October 3.
The film received generally positive reviews from critics and, as of October
2017, grossed over $2.3 million from DVD and Blu-ray sales.
The film explores themes of voodoo, evil doll, mental
institution, killer doll, serial killer.
The tone is dark and intense.